We've looked at how SageMaker can be used to create and train models and we've
我们学习了如何使用 SageMaker 创建和训练模型
looked at how the batch transform functionality can be used to test the trained model.
以及如何使用批量转换功能测试训练的模型
Now, we'll look at how you can deploy a trained model.
下面我们将学习如何部署训练的模型
In our case, we'll be deploying it by making it available at
我们将使端点能够访问部署的模型
an endpoint which is a supported way of deploying a model using SageMaker.
这是 SageMaker 支持的模型部署方式
We'll use the deployed model for the notebook itself,
我们将从 notebook 本身里使用部署的模型
but later on in this lesson,
但是稍后
we'll create a web app that can access a deployed model.
我们将创建一个能够访问部署的模型的网络应用
To follow along, navigate into
要跟着操作
the SageMaker folder and then inside of the tutorials folder,
请转到 SageMaker 文件夹 然后在 Tutorials 文件夹中打开
and open up the Boston Housing XGBoost High Level deploy notebook.
Boston Housing XGBoost High Level deploy notebook
To start with, we will be using the same dataset and creating
我们将使用与其他 Boston Housing notebook
the same sort of model as in the other Boston Housing notebooks.
一样的数据集并创建相同的模型
In particular, we'll be predicting the median cost of
我们将使用 XGBoost
a house in the Boston area using XGBoost.
预测波士顿地区的房价中位数
Since we've done this before,
因为之前已经讲解过这些步骤
I will go ahead and train the model now.
所以我将直接训练模型
Now, we've obtained the data,
我们获取了数据
done any processing that was required,
执行了所有的处理步骤
built the model, and trained it.
构建并训练了模型
Instead of creating a batch transform job to test our model,
但是这次我们不使用批转换作业测试模型
we're going to test it by first deploying it,
而是先部署模型
and then sending the test data to the deployed endpoint.
然后将测试数据发送给部署的端点
Using the high-level approach makes actually deploying the model very easy.
使用高阶方法部署模型非常简单
We simply call the deploy method of the trained model object making sure to
直接对训练的模型对象调用 deploy() 方法
specify the number of virtual machines we want to use and the type of virtual machine.
在这里指定虚拟机的数量以及类型
Currently SageMaker is preparing and then we'll run our deployed model.
目前 SageMaker 正在准备中 然后运行部署的模型
We'll come back once this is done.
运行完毕后再回来
As you can see, the model has now been deployed.
可以看到 模型已经部署了
So, what does this mean exactly?
到底是什么意思？
What this means is that SageMaker has created a virtual machine that
意思是 SageMaker 创建了一个虚拟机
contains our trained model that can be accessed at an endpoint,
其中包含我们训练的模型 该模型可以从端点访问
in other words, at a specific URL.
即从特定的 URL 访问
In the next video when we go into more detail,
在下个视频中讲解详细流程时
I'll show you how you can find this URL, but for now,
我将告诉你如何查找该 URL
the predictor object, which was returned by
暂时 deploy() 方法返回的 predictor 对象
the deploy method takes care of all of that for you.
将为你完成一切工作
In order to send data to our model's endpoint,
为了将数据发送给模型的端点
we can use the predict method of the predictor object that was returned.
我们可以使用返回的 predictor 对象的 predict 方法
However, the data that we provide to the predictor object needs to be serialized first.
但是 提供给 predictor 对象的数据必须先序列化
Fortunately, SageMaker provides this functionality for us
幸运的是 SageMaker 为我们提供了此功能
so long as you specify the type of data that our model expects.
只需指定模型需要的数据类型
In this case, we are going to be using
我们将使用 csv 数据
CSV data and so we can use the provided CSV serializer.
所以可以使用提供的 csv_serializer
Once our model has performed inference on each of the records that we sent it,
模型对发送的每条记录进行推理后
a result will be returned,
将返回结果
which would be the serialized predictions.
即序列化预测
This means that the result is a comma delimited string of results
对于每条记录来说 结果是按逗号分隔的字符串结果
for each record and so we need to convert it back to a numpy array,
我们需要将其转换为 numpy 数组
which is what we do right here.
也就是这一步的作用
Once we had the resulting data in a format that we can use,
一旦获得转换好格式的数据后
we can make a nice little graph to see how our model is doing.
我们可以绘制图形 看看模型的表现如何
Of course, we should expect this model to perform
当然 这个模型的效果
similarly to the other XGBoost models that we've made using the same dataset.
应该与使用同一数据集创建的其他 XGBoost 模型相似
The last step that must be completed is to shut down the deployed model.
最后一个必须完成的步骤是关闭部署的模型
Remember, that SageMaker has created
SageMaker 为你创建了一个虚拟机
a virtual machine for you that is hosting your trained model.
用来托管你训练的模型
This virtual machine will continue to run waiting
这个虚拟机将继续运行
for data to be sent to it until you shut it down.
等待你向其发送数据 直到你关闭它
Since the cost of running a deployed model is based on how long it is running for,
因为运行部署的模型按运行时长计费
when you no longer need an endpoint you need to shut it down.
所以不使用端点后 需要关闭端点